mysterious it's
mysterious and we just want encourage
people um you know in the um we will
shout you out we'll do a little dance uh
if you guys in the chat send us a Super
Chat whether it's one $2 three $3 $5 $10
you know we're looking to build hustles
on TV uh uh encourage writers to um to
to hire writers and to encourage um more
diversity in the media space so um you
know and shout out to all those that you
guys are amazing I'm just seeing a lot
of activity here um thank you guys so
much for um for how can I see the how
can I see the thread uh the thread is
actually on the top uh so you can see
the thread if you look on your are you
on a computer on on a uh if I pull it up
on my phone right here yeah or or is it
on if I it's on it's on here it's on
streamyard are you on a phone I'm on I
mean my iPad oh live comments holy crap
there's so many
yeah we're going through them anyways so
yeah we'll go through them as we go for
sure awesome Jared I like we have
reached an hour are you good to go a
little
longer yeah it depends how interesting
the questions are but sure okay awesome
we do have a round two lightning round
um that's going to be coming up uh
shortly but um
some I guess as an entrepreneur and
you're business person you're um you
know you're someone that you know a lot
of your friends maybe I don't know maybe
you're a lot of your friends that you've
grown up with will never experienced
some of the things that you've
experienced um you know because you have
a list of accomplishments you've worked
with lot of amazing people but you know
a lot of that stuff can be very
isolating and um you know because
there's a lot of people that don't
understand and if you are dealing with
people in the industry um industry tends
to be um you know all about business and
you know and what can I get from you so
you kind of find yourself in a box um
you know in a good place mind you you I
I'm sure you wouldn't trade what you're
doing for the world uh but at the same
time there's there's pockets of you know
um there there are pockets of being I
don't know if it's loneliness or but
there are Pockets where you know where
you feel like you can't express yourself
the way that you you want to now can you
do you identify with what I'm saying and
you know what sort of relationships do
you have with the friends that you grew
up with um you know uh people that are
not in the the the in the um music
industry
uh yeah I mean of course I identified
but I think what you're talking about is
something this is Ryan Perez with hustle
Zone jam session or sorry hustle Zone
jam session hustle Zone exclusiva and
this is why wonderful ho or co-host uh
Monica Black Diamond how's it
going oh you are
muted sorry about my goodness what's
wrong with with us today
listen welcome everybody to exclusiva
we're here having a good time bringing
you some amazing new shows and this is
one of them so I'm super excited how
about you Ryan I'm I'm I'm super excited
too um today's guest is uh very awesome
um so awesome that I've had his song
stuck in my head for three days stuck
three he's not kidding yeah it's he's
not kidding you guys now this song is
going viral right like I I see you know
a few uh people um on um our guest time
not timeline but stories and everyone's
doing their own version of it and it's
it's pretty cool um but you know he's
he's a great he's a great uh songwriter
and whatnot but before we get to our
amazing guest um let's talk how are you
doing what's what's going on in your
life uh
Monica like truth truth or like
hilarious truth or what side hilarious
truth give us give us hilarious give us
all you got by by the way shout out to
Tori she's like
[Music]
Jer we love you that's what it was like
so we got kente in the house hey K if
you guys can do us a good favor and
share this out to as many people as you
possibly can we need to get as much Good
Vibes like Tori says Vibes we need to
get some much uh we got to
get yeah hold on hold on you know Jared
got some like amazing amazing amazing
grossness amazing fans like they're the
best fans that I've seen so far like
they love him like wow yes I remember I
went on to one of his lives and they
were just going crazy but not like crazy
crazy like they're just so they're so
kind they're so nice they're so loving
so I'm super excited about this live
today I I am super excited too so we got
to do some house cleaning um first and
foremost uh folks um those who are in
YouTube don't forget you know Monica and
I have been uh you know hustle Zone in
it in its entirety has been we're going
on to our fifth year next year um you
know we've been volunteering our time
doing uh what we could to um make this
happen um for you guys and we have such
we have a lot of amazing guests that's
going to be just like Jared um that's
going to be on this broadcast so you
know um if you're in YouTube right now
if you have the power and the funds you
guys can support us through the Super
Chat where that funds are going to go is
hiring people of color especially um and
hire people to write to create content
um to also help us develop the world's
first living documentary it's technology
that allow s you it's pretty much
creating a video that's a Wiki like if
you guys look at Wikipedia you can you
can edit any any article that you want
and it's a community a living
documentary is a Wiki for a documentary
so we're looking for your support So if
you are in the YouTube chats don't
forget to send us a dollar $5 $10 $100
$100,000 but you know either way um
donate and then we also have a GoFundMe
campaign
um I don't know if I put that those
those links in the description but here
is the uh here is the the the link um
for uh the the GoFundMe and we wouldn't
be here without our proud sponsors um we
have um our first sponsor which is
flixer so flixer will will allow you to
um Flix year will allow you to uh edit
your videos in the cloud yes in the
cloud so um you no longer have to like
for all those graphic designers like
myself out there that have to do
everything on the computer it takes too
much time comp U Computing time Etc uh
CPU time and memory um where if you edit
in the cloud you have to rely on Amazon
servers to render everything you don't
got to worry about it you don't got to
work and you can you can edit anywhere
around the world so on your lapt top on
your phone you can edit videos so it's a
a pretty cool software if you guys want
definitely access to that just send me a
link and I'll send you an affiliate link
so that you can um um you can get access
to that and then finally um make sure if
you guys haven't done so already uh a
lot of our content that you're going to
see with hustle zone is going to be
right here on YouTube so for all the
people that are on Facebook and and
other places make sure to head over to
YouTube like And subscribe and hit that
that notification button
notification okay so um now uh let's see
here we have Patricia Murray in the
house what's going on Patricia welcome
Patricia so Monica is going to do the
honors and um she's going to do the
honors and read Our Guest bio and then
we're going to get to the show
let's go yeah okay so Jared Dylan is an
artist in every sense of word you could
think of so he has studied um he has
studied acting photography music um he
has won awards worked with look artists
like by all kinds of artists Davey Bowie
Madonna the Rolling Stones uh cplay seal
lanis maret like I love this guy
um and has won awards his draw Awards
sorry and has won awards for his
drawings paintings and songs so here we
go I want to present you guys our
bestest friend Jared
Dylan any second it's like it's like
magic and he say what's going on jar hey
I I love the background that you got
there it's h you know you got nice brick
you got a guitar there you got a helmet
and cus yeah this is actually the live
set for my weekly live stream I'm live
every Sunday at 800 PM Eastern awesome
this is where I go live from awesome
awesome and we got uh yeah so we got a
fan in the house she says you're a Kate
Tori says you're a Kate Tori and I go
way back she's been around since the
beginning pretty much that's awesome
that's awesome she's the
best so Jared we're gonna start this um
we're going to start this live like we
normally do in the hustle zone is you
know we are about the story behind The
Glory you know we know that you've done
some amazing things but take us back to
when you were a child um you know tell
us how what's your origin story how did
you get from where you are now or so
when you were then to to now
okay how how young are we talking you
want to he you go as young if you were
singing when you were two
boring let me know I started singing
when I was
15 wow yeah I actually so what happened
was in high school I was diagnosed with
Lyme disease I was running like Varsity
track I was playing sports and I I did
uh visual art my whole life but it was
like 15 years old when I got diagnosed I
was sleeping 20 hours a day and I was
like mentally I was completely there the
whole time so it was just very
frustrating and I would be laying in bed
uh with a guitar that I've that I had
had for years just kind of pounding out
my first songs and I started singing and
then from there I went on to the
University of Miami and studied music
and kind of changed my whole life as my
silver lining of uh lime disease wow
that's amazing now like you so you're
telling me that you started singing at
15 so you did did you know that you
could sing prior to that no clue not at
all like I would sing a lot um but it
wasn't very good and I'll look at videos
of myself and I was not a great singer I
would uh in my head I sounded amazing
but on recordings it was it could have
been so much better and honestly like
every time I would sing my dad would
always be like Jared stop singing and
then uh when I started taking it
seriously he became my biggest supporter
and you know I I auditioned for a band
the first band I ever auditioned for
he's like C have you ever sung before I
was auditioning as the singer I was like
no but I'm gonna I'm gonna go for it and
so we got me one professional uh like a
singing lesson right before the audition
and I made it yeah and that was the
beginning of the end I just just like
okay because a lot of people go
Beyond um over and Beyond they have
dreams of being a singer and and singing
funished stages and stuff like that so
you me to tell me that prior to 15 years
old there was no
inclination no dream that hey maybe I'll
try out singing and do songwriting on
top of that no all started at 50 I just
had a deep passion for attention love
detention
everybody very yeah yeah love love I
remember I remember I don't know why I'm
saying this out loud I remember from a
very young age just being like I have so
much love to give like I just feel so
much love in here I just want to share
it with the world and uh yeah and I
guess music kind of was my conduit
awesome awesome okay
so
well I wanted to ask you what is your
creative process like
uh it changes it changes from day to day
changes from song to song um
lately okay so there's two like main
processes that I've been honing in and
uh so one of them is sitting down with a
guitar or on the piano uh whatever
instrument I can actually play and
um this is cool okay this is uh I I
won't this this is uh something that
you'll only know if you've actually
collaborated with me if you've written a
song with me the way I start recession
is I have the collaborator or myself
whoever's going to be performing the
song I have them say oh and uh and then
I'll find whatever pitch they naturally
M at and that's the key that we write
the song in and so and and usually like
that also informs
whether it's a major or a minor song and
from that first chord I can always hear
where it wants to go and then the song
kind of the melody and the music really
come out all at once and when I hear
music there's always one Melody that
makes sense to me and uh and so I always
kind of let the song Make itself and
then I can uh
painstakingly write lyrics for months
but the words are very important to me
but so there's that
process and then what I've been working
on lately as I've been honing in my uh
production chops is actually producing a
beat that captures a Vibe and then just
writing a Topline to it which is also
something like I'll I'll if somebody
sends me beats uh if I have a publisher
sending beats or a collaborator sending
beats I'll Topline that so it's
something I'm comfortable with and just
writing lyrics and Melody is kind of
right right my what's gotten me into the
situations that I've been lucky enough
to be in that's awesome that's awesome
now uh when it comes to what what type
of music do you normally write you know
like what is the what is the
theme the
theme the theme or your brand or like
how would you how would you narrow down
you know some of the songs that you
write okay very tongue and cheek very
cheeky lot of
innuendo uh but always a silver lining h
no matter how sad depressing it gets I I
got to find the silver lining because uh
if not I've pretty much given
up but that's I think that's how I would
summarize it yeah why the why the Civil
Ling cver lining you know because I mean
there's so many ways of ending a song
and why did you choose that to be your
you know a way that people identify
you
uh all right I guess we'll get we'll get
deep and personal just quick into the
interview
okay I'm I'm
[Laughter]
like that's a good
question I didn't think about that yeah
h i mean so I I I told you I got into
music it music was my silver lining and
so I guess in a
way I'm like like I'm upset and angry
about so many
things and that's just not who I want to
be I don't want to be upset I don't want
to be angry um
and and so
maybe maybe in a sense it's selfish like
self-serving that the music also keeps
me going like songs like keep me on the
Edge songs like I really want it um
those are super positive and motivate
motivating to me and were written during
like the hardest struggles I've had to
go through you know it feels like a
constant battle pushing a boulder up a
hill uh trying to be heard and
appreciated as an artist and respected
and and you know like uh I
just even even when I'm struggling I'm
not going to sit there and wallow in it
I'm going to overcome and that's kind of
the Silver Lining that I want my entire
career
to put forth so it's going to just
naturally be reflected in my music I
suppose go ahead
Monica so what is one message you would
like to give to your
fans like what is your main
my when you have your friends yeah
because they love your music and you
have like I said earlier you have an
amazing like family of fans like your
tribe is I I went live one day with you
and to tell you the truth just the love
that you get from them I want I really
want to know what is the message you
want them to know in your music what is
it that you want to give to them well
first I want to say that all the love I
get from them is returned tenfold I love
them all so much and yeah that's I mean
I guess that's really what it is it's so
funny when you say the word fans it's
like that's a strange concept somebody's
just like but it's to me to me it feels
like a community of people that have
come together around uh common interests
and common goals and that's just you
know Finding joy and spreading love and
being happy so I guess the one thing I
got to say to my community is thank you
for being such a deep source
of love for me and fueling the P fueling
my passion for the music which brought
us together in the first place that's
awesome you got a lot of friends in that
you know we got uh Lula she says we love
you Luella so we love you uh and then uh
and then we had
um uh luchano he says uh Luca here from
Brazil this is amazing this is awesome
this is a full
house welcome everyone if you guys are
digging this interview so far just put a
one in the chat well put a one in the
chat um and and like I said if you guys
are on YouTube uh you know send us a a
Super Chat and we will shout you out um
on YouTube and then everybody else don't
forget to click on the GoFundMe uh
campaign after this is is all good um to
help support this this this broadcast
but uh Jared
so I noticed that with your you know
speaking of your fans and and whatnot
you know I I find that like listening to
your music um you know your music is
very it's relatable right and I you know
I can when I hear you singing about
certain subjects I'm like you know
what that's me that's me and I think
that a lot of the music that you that
you that you um that you talk about is
about some of your
relationships yeah and you know and
they've and they fuel a lot and maybe
they're well if that's the case I'm
sorry I'm sorry that you relate
so look what you did Jared look what you
did look what you did look what you did
Jared Jared do you find that your
relationships are you know um you know
like past
experiences um have fueled a lot of
those
songs yeah oh absolutely um almost all
of them every single almost on and and
do you find that um because you had you
know you have some heartbreak you have
some you know good times and and all
that and you know tell me a little bit
about your process of channeling some of
your old experiences uh through your
music uh yeah my the songs I write every
single song is uh based on experience
and like I think when I set forth to
write lyrics I more than anything I
would I love telling stories I like to
think of myself as a Storyteller but
more than anything I like to capture
emotion and really write the kind of
lyrics that allow the most room for
interpretation so that anyone can listen
to it and be like yeah I identify and
kind of apply their own experience to um
to what they're listening to what
they're hearing so when it comes to
writing down my
experiences uh in a sense
usually uh it it happens weeks if not
months after the breakup or after uh
whatever whatever event whatever emotion
I'm capturing I give it time to resonate
and understand it and it's not it's not
until usually I'm on the other side of
whatever I just went through that the
song is finished or really comes
out but then there's also songs like we
can't that uh was written so in the
moment that it was one of the most
cathartic experiences but uh the process
for that song song specifically I was in
a long-distance relationship with a girl
in California I'm out here in New Jersey
so literally opposite sides of the
country coast to coast and I flew out to
see her um well well she flew out to see
me and we had broken up at the end of
her visit and then I flew out to see I
had already purchased my ticket to fly
back to LA the next month so I went
anyway and I stayed with some friends
and I saw her and we went out um I I met
a bunch of her friends and her sister
and like that like after breaking up and
it was kind of dramatic and didn't end
very well and so literally the next day
after going out uh with in a big group
of people I had a studio session set up
to write we can't and it literally yeah
that song I I I sat back and I played
the whole trip in my mind and I was just
like and I like from getting off the
plane in La I was just like hello honey
glad to see your well having fun put my
heart through
hell uh and then uh you know and it just
kind of took on from there and uh and
literally that that song is a
stepbystep recount of that trip to La um
and then that writing session and then
everything was finished
uh the song was almost done I just had
to write the bridge and I'm in the
studio and she calls me and I ignore
that call by the way quick disclaimer no
bad blood I love this girl she's an
amazing person and um yeah she like
she's a nurse and she's you know an
essential worker on the front end of
this like uh this pmic and she's doing
love doing the Lord's work right now
she's really she's an amazing person but
um long distance is a real pain in the
ass and then also I left for Ireland for
a year and I barely talked to anybody
back in the States for a year uh so it
just it was a doomed relationship
unfortunately as they all are or have
been um that my yeah so
anyway she gives me a call she gives me
a call while we're while I'm in the
studio working on the song and I ignore
the call and then I write if you call me
and I'm busy just assume I'm
satisfied and that was the bridge so
it's like that was the most real time uh
song that ever kind of came out wow
that's amazing uh all based on
experience though all based on
experiences so that's why I can relate
and you know and I think a lot of people
can you know relate to that for
sure so Jared what has been your out of
all of those songs what has has been
your favorite song that you've actually
performed you know cuz there's so many
good ones it's kind of hard to pick one
right I knew this was gonna kill you I
gotta choose favorites now you gotta
think you gotta Nar it down yeah okay my
favorite song that I've ever performed
not that I've ever written that I've
ever
performed yeah would probably
be
um Maybe I'm Amazed
how
come Paul McCartney is my favorite
songwriter of all time I just worship
that
guy and uh maybe is just one of the
greatest love songs of all time as
well and I was not uh that song just has
a lot of sentimental value for me and I
it was one of the first songs I learned
to play on the
piano so wow I just really enjoyed
playing that song also belting that
because it sits really nice in my voice
so nice so we got so Luciano says um or
Luca says Jared do you have a release
date for the new song dude Luca I just
released the track on Friday I was gonna
say I wasna be like there's another
one we're gonna freak out here
Jared so much music coming out too I
have I've got I've got uh I've written
hundreds of songs but I have maybe like
a back catalog that I could probably
release like three albums right now if I
needed to but
um that I don't have a set date I could
I don't even want to say a date because
I don't want to jinx it hopefully soon
let's say
that sooner rather than later let's say
ideally within six
weeks ideally but I'm not committing to
anything he's lying can't hold me to
it just wait it's actually fine he's
lying it's gonna be three
no he told me something different it's
tomorrow just
kidding so um when it comes to um you
know because you've you've the one thing
that is not really all over the place
but the fact is is that you've you've
written you've performed alongside a lot
of celebrities and and people well known
in the music industry
uh you know who who were the people that
um um that you've worked with and what
were you what were your overall
experience with uh working with all
these talented musicians and
songwriters uh so I guess the first
question is
who um I I think the first time I ever
opened for like a big artist was Andy
Grammar and that was awesome that was uh
I had just graduated college
and I got to go down to the Jersey Shore
and play on the beach like on a on so
there were just hundreds of people on
the beach right and I was on this uh big
wooden I guess like balcony and looking
out at the ocean and a mob of people um
underneath you know and it was just it
was the coolest experience ever uh
like I I played a handful of songs
completely acoustic it was uh for a
radio station as well and got to hang
out with Andy gramar a little bit and it
went so well that I I got to open for
him again uh in Rhode Island and yeah it
was um yeah that he was an awesome dude
and his fans oh man this the saddest and
um it's the saddest story uh at at the
second gig that I opened for Andy gramar
I got I got to like I got to mingle with
the audience afterwards and I just for
hours like it was a line of people that
were just coming up to me just to talk
to me which the first time in my life
that had ever happened and uh it
was such an amazing experience and
something that uh brought me so much
drive and focus in what I wanted to uh
keep reaching for
and I found out a week later that one of
the girls that I got to speak to um did
not make it home that night
and uh her mom reached out to me just to
thank me for bringing her so much joy
because uh she would not stop talking
about me and then that
was that that was like there are moments
like that that
that come up every so often right that
I'm like that's why that's why I to to
connect to people on a level like that
is why I make
music wow that's amazing now um we have
to I'm just going to check in if
anyone's in Facebook uh just put a
number one in the chats uh let us know
um you know tor's still here we got
um I cannot I don't know what this
person is saying but uh can you read
that
Monica
sure I think this is
um what's it called Portuguese
Portuguese oh no Spanish yeah that's
why um I think is
estyle no no style looks like yeah no P
um yeah I'm gonna speak in
Spanish Jared
okay um so go right ahead mine oh
yours awesome and and like we said if
you're in YouTube send us a Super Chat
and we will definitely um will
definitely um shout you out today um on
hustle exclusiva so uh Jared we're going
to go into um because you know we've
kind of I we don't want this to be a
typal interview where we talk about your
music and how you write your songs and
you know what you think about Paul
McCartney you know we wanted we want to
also get a you know better understanding
because you know a lot of you know the
work that you've
done I'm not saying you're clean cut but
you know I think a lot of the um you
know you you're quite you're private and
you're and um you know there's a certain
image that is being portrayed um with
your brand so we wanted to ask you a few
question questions just so that the your
fans and you know everyone can kind of
get to know how amazing guy you are um
so what um in terms of like where do you
think at this point um you would have
been had you not done
music I'd be an
architect architect and how how how how
so like so like what was that a parents
dream was that your dream you know kind
of explain the story behind that um well
like I said I was always into visual art
and to me AR I I just like creating you
know creating has always been a passion
and uh in high school I was I was taking
drafting classes and Architectural
design courses and I was it was amazing
that my high school even offered it but
uh then I got sick and started making
music and found a passion for it and and
so it was something that I never felt
with architecture but I know that that
was my plan I had I went to the
University of Miami and before I was
interested in music I had been down
there to look at the architecture school
and I was planning on going to the
University of Miami no matter what but
it was either going to be for
architecture or music and at the end uh
art went out much to my parents
dismay wow oh I mon was hold on one
second she was removed hold on let me
just remove you here go go ahead sorry
say that what sorry can you re say that
last part again Jared yes art one out
much to my parents
dismay yes I mean like you know that's
kind of um you know because I went the
art direction as well and and you know
so did Monica it's kind of like um you
know you have to kind of do you you know
where you find the most you know most
passion in things and are you you know
just a follow-up question before Monica
asked her question like do you think
that um you're going to be doing music
for the rest of your life is that kind
of what you um you know where you see
yourself in the
future I want to be I really yeah of
course I'm never not going to be making
music um that I I've I've written uh
idea I have ideas that I've already that
I've begun writing for I don't know if
it's going to be TV film whatever it is
but I've created this whole universe
that I can't wait to tell this story I
can't wait to share the story with the
world um I've got fashion design I've
got paintings and stuff that I've that
I've created and just you know I
uh I I I want to create and I want to
reach a level of success where I have
the opportunity to create just whatever
I want uh it's always going to be
centered around um entertainment I'm
sure uh just because that has proven to
be the way I can connect to people the
best but who's to say that I don't uh
design a building one day you know why
why put myself in that box but right
right I but I I will definitely be
making music for the rest of my life and
I'll be creating for the rest of my life
um it's
uh it's something
that every day I wake up and I might not
be where I want to be I but I'm
doing everything I
can uh and everything that I do is
something I'm passionate about so at the
end of the day
that's a life well lived that's awesome
that's
awesome so what are your biggest goals
for your life what progress have you
made and are you
um what's the
word happy with the progress that you
made so far like what is what is your
end goal or if there's such a thing
I'm happy I'm I'm definitely happy with
the progress that I've made
because uh like make no mistake trying
to do anything in entertainment on your
own hardest hardest thing you could sign
up for it doing anything alone is
incredibly difficult and that's why I
mean surrounding yourself with the right
people is so
important and I don't know that I have
so so it's hard it's like a hard
question um I've taken some terrible
advice I've been taking taken advantage
of uh for you know the quality of the
content that I can create and then on
top of that I've been doing it all alone
so every single thing that you see me
put out uh in order to get that done I
had to go out and do that and it's very
difficult for me as a a creative person
who gets distracted so
easily that um to to not lose focus and
not just want to lock myself away and
create art that no one will ever see but
right that was like one of the first
lessons I learned and one of
the one of the first lessons I learned
was
that uh you can't do it alone mhm
and what was said to me that resonated
so much
was there are people out there that are
way more talented than you and they will
never be heard because they don't know
how to Market themselves and they don't
know they don't understand business
right and for so
[Music]
long I was so worried
that I I I wasn't worried I was I was
very accepting of that for so long I
figured
like that's that's fine I need to get on
my business grind and then uh only
recently did I realize being such a
perfectionist over everything that I
do is turning me into the person who
will never be
hurt and uh I guess that's a
double-edged sword maybe I maybe I like
my art more maybe people would like my
art more than what is currently popular
but that doesn't matter if they never
hear it or see
it right so I'm going off on such a
tangent right now I don't even remember
the question no but you're talking about
your progress your progressing goals
there it is the progress yeah
but I've always been the kind of person
to overthink everything and uh I'm so
hyper aware of the moment that it's
really nice like uh in some in some
sense like certain experiences feel so
surreal because I'm like I'm going to
look back on this and it's going to be a
moment to look back on but
uh but when I look at my progress
over the last 10 years I've been making
music now for 10
years and uh
I know that I've made so many mistakes
that I could be a lot further than I
am and but I'm proud to be where I am
and and what were some of those mistakes
because I mean there's a lot of people
um especially fans I mean a lot of fans
want to do what you're doing um and some
of them can't you know so they kind of
live through
the artists that they they like to watch
but for those who want to get into the
music industry I mean it's not the music
industry is not that um it's not that
easy you know you have to deal when
you're dealing with record labels you're
dealing with you know advances and
having to recoup um a lot of artists
don't recruit on you know some of the
records that they put out um you know
putting them in a financial bind um I
know now in the music industry a lot of
people are going independent um
but you know even with that being said
being independent you don't really sell
a lot like you know you know the album
sales are not like they were you know in
the early 90s the late 90s and the early
2000s right so you know you're going to
have to you're you're having to tour you
have to do all this other stuff so you
know what are some of the valuable
advice for this
generation um you know of artists that
are are looking to come up like what
would you advise them with some of the
mistakes that you've you've encountered
I think uh there's a massive
misconception around what it means to be
an independent
artist um just because you're
independent doesn't mean you're not
answering to somebody doesn't mean
you
uh like to the amount of time money and
energy you have to invest into being an
independent artist
uh just to maintain your ownership of
whatever it is you're creating the
rights to your Masters whatever it is
that you're telling yourself is the
reason you'd rather be independent than
signed to a major
label is like you C 100% of nothing is
still nothing and uh and that's an
extreme an extreme idea but at the end
of the day I think you need to focus on
what it is uh not focus have some
clarity on what it is you're trying to
do and if you're trying to reach as many
people as possible a major label would
be the way to go and if you're in it for
the money you're in it for the wrong
reason
because uh that's that's going to
reflect in everything you do and I just
don't want to do anything for the money
and that's the worst thing any business
person could say the worst thing I
shouldn't say this on a live interview
but I'm not I'm not writing music to
make money I'm writing music because
it's what I love and if I could turn
that into a living and resonate with so
many people that there's a value that I
bring value to people's lives I want
like that's the best business advice I
can give you right now give anybody
watching right now is be
valuable uh create value and I mean just
from you saying like you identify with
my
music that's the most valuable thing in
the world to
me I I I would do
everything exactly the same just to hear
that wow so uh so business advice if you
ask like what would my learn the
business learn
business uh you can't do it
alone can't do it alone it's not worth
it to do it alone because then who are
you going to celebrate with and uh and
this is the biggest one for me uh never
compromise and that's and that's why I
say what I say never compromise your
voice uh because for me personally I
felt in moments where I did not have the
music sound the way I wanted it to sound
but I uh but I did I did it anyway
because I was being told like was I'm I
was my hands were tied like it was do
this because this is how you become
successful first of all nobody knows
what is going to hit and what's not and
if you don't believe in it yourself then
it's not it's not gonna hit exactly
don't ever compromise your
voice and and there are plenty of people
that have been so successful
and over doing whatever it is they were
told to do or whatever it is they
thought would sell
and while I would never want to be one
of those people I'm sure that there is a
lack of fulfillment in there somewhere
and it's probably one of the reasons you
see such a dissatisfaction among some of
the most successful artists in the
world wow great answers great answers uh
just wanted to shout out to everyone in
the chat like it's just filled with
people uh talking uh and um you know uh
we want to thank you guys folks and I
just want to do another shout out to our
you know sponsors Fier flixer you know
um edit your videos in the cloud um you
know should you guys are if you're
interested if you are into video editing
or anything like that and you want to
try out um the the the software just uh
put a two in the chat and then we'll
message you after the the that the live
is done and give you a exclusive access
to it so uh you know the other thing too
so we have a few things that are being
said so uh JD says uh I don't know how
to pronounce I don't know what they said
but means I love you
all I don't I don't know what language
that is I'm like nervous to say it but
he's saying it means I love you all
means I love you all love you
yeah scream it screaming with
but I almost I'm almost certain that I
said it with a perfect
accent you know you did you did I'm
pretty sure awesome and then uh luchano
says could you talk about the experience
of the clip with fans in I really want
it oh Luca he's in the video that's why
I says that
oh yeah so so like I said I'm on the of
EXP experiencing music right now and on
one one week uh maybe a month before the
song actually got released um I said on
the live stream I'm like I need to make
a video and I can't leave the house I'm
quarantined here so why don't you all if
you want to be in the video uh let me
know tag me on your story or whatever
and I'll send you a prompt for what I
need from you and the concept was what
do you really the song's called I really
want it and the prompt was what do you
really want to when the stay-at home
orders released
and we got people from all over the
world every continent every habitable
continent and it was it was the most uh
amazing and uh rapid like quick uh
turnaround of all time I think the video
was completed in a week a week and a
half maybe and I animated and edited the
whole thing myself uh had everybody send
me video clips of them holding up signs
that they made I even have if I step off
camera literally a second um these are
the signs these are examples of signs uh
this was my sister she really wanted to
go back to school and this was Max he
really wanted to have a party uh in
hindsight
I I really wish I wrote potty with a W
because it's um but that's fine we don't
have to talk about that too it's
fine uh yeah so we got people from all
around the world Luca makes an
appearance in there um it's uh just it
was an amazing experience to see how
people from every corner of the
globe had so much in common everybody
was putting in similar ideas and I
couldn't use all of the submissions but
the ones that I did get to use uh were
just you know know it it was so
heartwarming and it's still going on if
people want to hold up a sign and put it
in their story I share every single one
so awesome and then the the last
question is have you ever heard any
Brazilian music kind of
question best music in the world
tall young and
lovely yeah
awesome come on
so Jared um you speaking about the that
that song How You released and how you
got to that
how how I mean let's go before that how
is it that covid has affected you um and
your work minus that song because
obviously that's what happened but how
has it affected you being at home kind
of because I mean myself I work in home
so I'm kind of used to it but yet
obviously we have those needs that we
want to go out or want to do something
or sometimes even just be inspired to
work or to be creative right so how is
that um how have you take like taking
that like experience so far I'm sure
very much like everyone else in the
world it's completely changed my whole
way of interacting with the world and
it's been struggle honestly I had I had
a month worth of gigs booked in Miami
that just were completely cancelled and
it it's like you know it's a lot of my
money comes from live performance but in
the in the meantime I was able to start
up a freelance graphic design and
animation business because that's
something I've been doing for myself as
well as other artists for a period of
time and entrepreneurs who are starting
their own business buiness I'll help
them build a brand kit and um design ads
for them or product photos so I was able
to launch this uh broken Planet media is
the name of my yeah Media company and
check it out you guys check it out BPM
broken Planet media uh it's uh yeah it's
that's it's my Instagram broken Planet
media it's got some photos on there I'm
so not active on that page because I've
got Jay Dylan music that I do everything
through which is my whole personality
but it's a it's a mostly Word of Mouth
business but I have been able to sustain
myself in the meantime with graphic
design and animation in addition to
releasing new music and working
collaborating with people remotely I
actually just two weeks ago or maybe it
was even last week I don't know they all
blur together now but but uh let's say
let's say last week I just did my first
ever not first ever my first in-person
collaboration since lockdown
started so I'm getting out there
again okay and uh folks in the chat we
still see I'm just I thought I saw
something there um okay no I can't
pronounce this this is again in
uh something from iima
yeah I don't
know yeah so
Monica work with work with dot dot dot
dot dot
dot mysterious it's
mysterious and we just want to encourage
people um you know in the um we will
shout you out we'll do a little dance uh
if you guys in the chat send us a super
chat whether it's one $2 $3 $5 $10 you
know we're looking to build hustles on
TV uh uh encourage writers to um to to
hire writers and to encourage um more
diversity in the media space so um you
know and shout out to all those that you
guys are amazing I'm just seeing a lot
of activity here um thank you guys so
much for um for how can I see the how
can I see the thread uh the thread is
actually on the top uh so you can see
the thread if you look on your are you
on a computer on on a uh if I pull it up
on my phone right here yeah or or is it
on if I it's on it's on here it's on
streamyard are you on a phone I'm on I
mean my iPad oh live comments holy crap
there's
so we're going through them anyways so
we'll go through them as we go for sure
awesome Jared I like we have reached an
hour are you good to go a little
longer yeah it depends how interesting
the questions are but sure okay awesome
we're going we do have a round two
lightning round um that's going to be
coming up uh shortly but um
some I guess as an entrepreneur and your
business person you're um you know
you're someone that you know a lot of
your friends maybe I don't know maybe
your a lot of your friends that you've
grown up with will never experience some
of the things that you've
experienced um you know because you have
a list of accomplishments you've worked
with a lot of amazing people but you
know a lot of that stuff can be very
isolating and um you know because
there's a lot of people that don't
understand and if you are dealing with
people in the industry um industry tends
to be um you know all about business and
you know and what can I get from you so
you kind of find yourself in a box um
you know in a good place mind you you I
I'm sure you wouldn't trade what you're
doing for the world uh but at the same
time there's there's pockets of you know
um there there are pockets of being I
don't know if it's loneliness or but
there are Pockets where you know where
you feel like you can't express yourself
the way that you you want to now can you
do you identify with what I'm saying and
you know what sort of relationships do
you have with the friends that you grew
up with um you know uh people that are
not in the the the in the U music
industry uh yeah I mean of course I
identified but I think what you're
talking about is something that
everybody has those experiences that are
hard for them to articulate and that's
like one of the things
that uh I
have pushed myself
to see in everyone is that everybody's
got their own experience and no matter
what their experience is it's going to
be unique to them and I'll never be able
to understand their experience no matter
what they do no matter who they are they
could be in entertainment and I still
won't understand their experience and
where they came from and what they had
to
overcome because I'm not them I didn't
have to live it the way that they did so
in a sense that's a sad answer because
you're alone no matter what doesn't
matter and uh and I choose to go a
little deeper and say well we're all
alone which means we're all alone
together and that's why the one thing
that I really love to practice and and I
don't preach but the one thing that I
would love to
um spread more than anything is just
understanding and that's like an
understanding that we just don't know
you don't
understand world would be a better place
if there was more understanding is all
like what an interesting perspective you
know we are all alone but we're all
alone
together Silver Lining I see a theme I'm
I'm telling you the Silver Linings get
me through it's just I don't really have
much of a choice
yeah that's a great that's a great
answer Jared I was wondering I'm gonna
ask you for a big favor do you think
it's possible that you could sing us
something that
would that you know anything anything
you want and and tell us why you picked
that
song I would love to I haven't played
this song for a really long time
and I just so happen to have a
guitar look at that you can't even see
it down here which is GNA be cooler yeah
I have my stick over here well like I
said I'm on the set I got all my
instrument I have a ukulele over here
you're the screen is literally sitting
on a piano um oh really a keyboard yeah
you're on the keyboard um I
uh I just said like we've been talking
about silver lining
and this song is one of the first songs
I ever wrote so forgive me I have
to uh this just
like I I don't know what it is like my
songs to me personally when I tap that
vein of
creativity it's
uh it's almost prophetic where like
they get more true to me over time and I
love those songs that as I age they age
with me and this is my first DP that I
ever recorded was with Anthony resta and
karotti
sua um and they brought this song to
life introduced me to recorded music and
everything and just this song has always
been something that
one is about Silver
Linings um
and to gets more true over time for
me so
hopefully you think I should keep the
headphones in for this or yeah go ahead
yeah yeah let me know how it sounds
[Music]
[Applause]
how's that sound so far sounds good so
far good all right well I'm gonna I'm
gonna start singing
now okay we let
[Music]
you rain days all those rude Awakenings
I seem to lost touch with my brain I
build the bridge to burn it down again
and this one for theack
times I broke my back just trying to
keep together at the
same but when I take your breath away I
might forget to give it
back
back glad to know that it's all worth it
in the end why can't things be
[Music]
after long night sound asleep I lost
look now what they've cost I finally
realize what it means to
[Music]
important beautiful yeah
W Jared beautiful Jared why you got to
do that make me all
emotional I'm sorry hopefully that one
stuck in your head for the next three
days oh jar don't do that you're so mean
sorry yeah that was great that was
awesome so uh we have uh we have reached
the end of this interview so we're GNA
go
to
um the lightning round part two
so
lightning
okay this is why Jared is the singer and
and
I but um I don't know what you're
talking about I know he's such such a
hater
ha whatever ran whatever okay Jared talk
talking or
texting
talking
FaceTime FYI FaceTime yeah me
too I would say uh voem
messaging voice you voice message
constantly I get like messages they're
all audio record I got to listen to
every single one before yes you do you
know why you know what my problem is is
like I have this issue like when I read
I feel like I'm not understanding the
person I feel like if I send a voice
message you feel my words and you feel
in my tone and if I'm mad or if I'm not
cuz sometimes I'll write something
everyone thinks it's like I'm being mean
or I'm being too forward so when I act
when I it's happened they're like what
the heck's up with you and I'm like no
this is what I meant and they're like ah
you said it so nicely like yeah you
should know me by now so yeah I rather I
rather very awesome uh so um favorite
day of the week Sunday live streams 800
PM experiencing music Baby there you go
plug plug
Monica let's
do Monday I guess Monday okay because
you start we what an odd what an odd
answer yeah because Monday is usually a
terrible day for most people because
they gotta go no I know but you know
what though I hate like CU we're you
Ryan come on we work every single day of
Our Lives but I think that Monday is
like the starting of a new week so you
should be excited regardless because
you're like like I'm you want to like
face all your goals every I mean I could
say every single day but Monday for me
is like the starting of of awesomess
what goals you tackle this week exactly
get I got you come
on come on man come
on well okay whatever favorite day of
the week oh yeah I said that favorite
City besides the one that we live
in our favorite what our city so
favorite City besides the the one that
you live in Oh that's oh that's a tough
one that's that's the hardest
question which one I guess I'm
considering New York to be the one I
live
in so New
York Che Miami
Miami a okay
what about you
Monica um well I'm in South America
right now which would be monly be they
the city which is
amazing um if I had to pick I'd
probably I I really
like oh that's hard I don't want to go
to IR City Calgary but I I would I like
more van Vancouver BC is type of Shir
I mean you kind of live there too
so whatever Jared whatever I don't know
it just feels like you're cheating I
feel like you're cheating to okay sure
let's do yeah no I I'm here technically
I'm here in in Uruguay so I can say
Calgary or BC technically yeah okay
technically you're right F I am
I'm uh nickname your parents used to
call
you
oh Monica Mona
Monita theia theia is my middle name
theia um yeah oh yeah that's it
Ora what about you Jared those are all
really nice nicknames my parents were
not so I don't know if I say names on
the air uh J man JB J man
JB okay okay awesome and last song Oh no
we'll get that one that one's not
relevant uh would you rather be able to
speak a language or every language of
the world or talk to
animals that's hardcore question like I
just want to
do right I'm going animals for sure are
you kidding animals
animals yeah yeah because like because
people even if I didn't speak their
language I would be able to I would be
able to communicate with a human being
uh with like Pictionary fantastic at
Pictionary so like I would be totally
down with hog hieroglyphics tell the
story through pictures but if I could
also speak to animals that's a
superpower
now yes yes that is it totally I I I
agree with you uh scale from one to 10
how good of a or did I miss you Monica
you said yeah you're
rude I'm just joking no I was agreeing
with him so it's all good so it's all
good okay so scale of one to 10 how good
of a driver are you so we'll start with
Jared uh what's the setting are we just
talking getting from A to B or
like okay both settings um
8.5 8.5 what about you
Monica I'll be very
honest you never asked me that I'll be
very honest I was in a a really big uh
car crash in general so for me I have a
um it's funny because I I've never
actually really talked about it but in
Calgary I was in actually a really big
car crash so I have like a phobia
of driving I know how to but I kind of
stay away from it because of that oh I
didn't know so what you're saying is
you're out of practice you're not a very
good
driver it's weird because I know I can
drive craziness like gangster hardcore
but oh yeah yeah when that
happened you
know yeah but the thing 10 is what the
question was like where
we yeah um yeah no I'm good driver it's
just since that happened I never I just
choose not to which has been really hard
for me but I got so especially being in
uguay I'm over here people are more into
taking the bus and walking and and I
like that it's more European is in that
sense
um yeah I'd just rather do that or just
gonna shower that works zero folks zero
uh you killed me on that yeah so uh tail
fill in this fill in the blank um Taylor
Swift
is Monica he comes to me
um Taylor
Swift Taylor Swift is is that what you
said fill in the
blank is a very kind
woman Jared an
artist awesome in visibility or super
strength
oh wow can I just pick
both
no I don't I didn't make the W but I
know that's against them that was
definitely okay so be invisible or super
strength
strong oh I think
I I would I would say uh
invisible invis because then I could go
to any soccer games I want to down here
and I could just get in without anybody
knowing it and then you know I could get
get it wherever I want to go period
tells me a lot about
you what about what about you most
devious
superpower
well like I said at the beginning of the
interview I had a deep love of attention
my entire life so invisibility would
just not be the superpower for me um and
also super strength is like the most
ostentatious superpower so yeah I'm
gonna go with super strength super
strength okay and Mr
Superman second last question um is it
wrong for uh for a vegetarian to eat
animal crackers or vegan animal crackers
so we'll go with
listen go ahead go Jerry we're talking
about morality yeah then I don't think
it's a moral issue but if you give me a
moment to look it up I don't know that
animal crackers are gluten-free so it
may not be
appropriate smarty pants smarty pants
everybody we got a smarty pants
here D look it up and I'll answer too
all right I'll look at it team J let's
go and while we're doing this uh so this
is um hoo is that how I pronounce that
KKK he's saying oh what is that like
okay okay what is it so we got um you
got this you got this you got this you
got this you got this so what's the
what's the
ingredients uh I just Googled and
crackers vegan friendly question mark
and it said
yes that was so
awesome okay I would it say yes they're
vegan friendly animal crackers aren't
real animals of course and the original
Confections by scoffers don't contain
any direct animal ingredients like dairy
or eggs the answer is what was the
question is it a yes or a no
vegans eat animal crackers yes that is
the smartest answer that we've had the
only person the only
person yeah D that didn't just answer to
answer I love that I have I have the
answer to every question in the entire
world right here wow look at you you
look at you all smarty over there
so so final question and this is uh
directed to Jared uh what's next for
you um probably going to finish this
coffee my sister just made some cookies
and I'm going to go upstairs and eat my
body weight in chocolate chip cookies
yummy and then it's Saturday night so
I'll just do some laundry and pass out
around seven oh wait it's
8:20 there goes my
night the end the
yeah I don't know quarantine lifestyle
I've got so much music coming guys I um
I can't wait to release it I can't wait
to share it with you um I have so much
on the horizon that I want to share with
you that I just don't want to jinx it
because I'm very superstitious in weird
ways um but here how about
this oh Magic
Ball uh what's next for
me cannot predict now that's crazy I
knew it Jared thing to
say damn you know what's funny is I uh I
asked the I don't think Monica was on
the on the call before but I said will
this be the best interview on live
interview on YouTube history and he just
said yes and I gotta say best interview
I've ever had awesome oh
Jared don't me cry don't cry would you
would you ever come back
Jared uh yeah I didn't realize I had to
leave
but you're getting kick doctor yeah all
right well yeah we would invite you we
have a show called um hustles on jam
session where you know we integrate with
the fans the fans come into the chats um
and then we ask everyone a question so
you're it's like a Fanfare experience uh
with you being the guest so if you're
open to coming to one of those shows
sounds awesome we'd be happy to have you
yeah yeah I'd love to that yeah and um
the other thing too is that we have one
last thing that we got to do before we
sign out so this is a call and response
um people in hip hop world know what a
call and response is but a call and
response is if I say something then you
say something afterwards so what what
I'm say is welcome to the and then we
need you to scream hustle Zone as loud
as you can and um like gon with you
needs to disturb all the family members
and for those who are watching in the
chats please make sure to let us know
how well did you like this interview did
you guys like this interview um you know
put a number one in the chat um and um
you know and will you recommend this
interiew to friend and and once this
interview is done you can go in and you
can share it um to people that you know
weren't here that weren't able to uh to
watch and don't forget folks send us a
Super Chat we will definitely shout you
guys out and um you know and then we
also put I put in the the link or in the
the chat sections um our GoFundMe
account uh for you to donate to hustle
Zone TV the world's first living
documentary so I want to thank everybody
for for coming in today so Jared you
ready so dope hustle hustle Zone welcome
to the
hustle that was that was that was weak
Jarry we got to do this one more time it
needs to be come on
man has to be loud and it has to disturb
the peace
so I'm not trying to disturb the peace
on a Saturday night but all right okay
welcome to the
hustle okay thank you that was great
that was amazing so thank you so much
Jared where can we find
you everywhere literally everywhere
Spotify YouTube Apple Instagram check me
out Jill music Sundays at 8:00 pm I'm
live but I'm always there and I try to
respond to every message I get on
Instagram which takes up a lot of my
time but I'm there so awesome come find
me come find me and for all those were
that were in the chat thank you uh
Patricia we you had a lot of people from
all over the world in this chat you know
we have from Barcelona from
Brazil it's amazing so thank thank you
guys so much and um you know we'll be
here you know we have what's our next
show
Monica it for which part for hustles
exclusiva it'll be in two weeks in two
weeks F two weeks two weeks every two
weeks we'll be having and featuring an
artist uh on Friday and Saturday so
watch out you guys you guys will get
notifications on our Instagram and our
Facebook and on YouTube everywhere so
you guys you got to make sure subscribe
to hustle Zone because heck while you
doing that press the what do you call it
the little we Sayan in Spanish the the
ringer the what the heck is that thing
called The Ringer the the Bell hit the
Bell I'm like
ringer um so make sure you touch that
because then you guys will get the
notification as well as we go live so
yeah awesome all right well thank you
guys so much and we will talk to you
guys later peace and and I really mean
that peace because the world is going
through so much right now and we just
need some healing and so we're gonna end
our shows by just love and peace so we
love you guys from the bottom of our of
our hearts and we just wish the world
you know can get some time to heal okay
have a good one and we are gone bye